<<<<<<< HEAD
{"questions":[{"question":"What instrument is used to measure angles?","answers":["Protractor","Pair Of Compasses","Ruler"],"rightAns":"Protractor","qid":"1","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"Who does Mark jilt in an episode of the peep show?","answers":["Mike wazowski","Sophie","Jane"],"rightAns":"Sophie","qid":"4","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What's the best quality street chocolate?","answers":["Green Triangle","Purple One","Orange Creme"],"rightAns":"Orange Creme","qid":"6","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What is the first letter of the Greek alphabet?","answers":["Alto","Theta","Alpha"],"rightAns":"Alpha","qid":"8","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What is a barracuda?","answers":["Dinosaur","Fish","Soap"],"rightAns":"Fish","qid":"9","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0}],"participants":0,"timetaken":[],"q":0}
=======
{"questions":[{"question":"Who does Mark jilt in an episode of the peep show?","answers":["Mike wazowski","Sophie","Jane"],"rightAns":"Sophie","qid":"4","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What is the first letter of the Greek alphabet?","answers":["Alto","Theta","Alpha"],"rightAns":"Alpha","qid":"8","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What instrument is used to measure angles?","answers":["Protractor","Pair Of Compasses","Ruler"],"rightAns":"Protractor","qid":"1","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What's the best quality street chocolate?","answers":["Green Triangle","Purple One","Orange Creme"],"rightAns":"Orange Creme","qid":"6","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0},{"question":"What's the capital of Norway?","answers":["Oslo","Beanstaple","Coruscant"],"rightAns":"Oslo","qid":"3","numRestarts":0,"numRight":0,"numWrong":0,"numParticipants":0,"timeTaken":0}],"participants":0,"timetaken":[],"q":0}
>>>>>>> df732d422a1fb04799a302cca59a5d47830b1137
